<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>s1m</title>
    <link>http://localhost:34941/</link>
    <description>Recent content on s1m</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:34941/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>On idealism and materialism</title>
      <link>http://localhost:34941/posts/materialism-vs-idealism-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:34941/posts/materialism-vs-idealism-1/</guid>
      <description>Summary In this blog post, I will outline my views on epistemic idealism and materialism. I argue that in Western culture, there has been a distinct cultural shift from idealist to materlialist thinking, and that this trend is clearly represented in various types of speech in English. I argue that this has lead to the death of religion, and generally, the lack of understanding of past texts and inner reasoning by modern people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece and the Death of Admiral Nelson</title>
      <link>http://localhost:34941/posts/greece-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:34941/posts/greece-2024/</guid>
      <description>During my recent trip to Greece, there were several moments that stood out to me.&#xA;Corinth Corinth was the last town that I visited during my trip. Visiting ancient Corinth was interesting since I was actually able to walk through the streets of the ancient city. I realized that these were the same streets walked by St. Paul.&#xA;For this light momentary affliction is preparing for us an eternal weight of glory beyond all comparison, 2 Corinthians 4:17</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typewriter-like internet presence</title>
      <link>http://localhost:34941/posts/typerwiter-presence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:34941/posts/typerwiter-presence/</guid>
      <description>My friend commented that `this is the second-best type of internet presence, after having none&amp;rsquo; after I showed this blog. I fully agree, and in this post, I want to talk about the state of the internet and possible motivations for making an anonymous internet blog. Maybe you will be inspired to do the same, and we can RETVRN to a low-entropy 90s internet, or at least understand its value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>first post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:34941/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:34941/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>hello&#xA;this is the first post on this blog, april 4 2024. ive just destroyed some pour soul&amp;rsquo;s hugo css to make this&#xA;the point of this site is to post takes/thoughts. there are some philosophical reasons to having your own blog and expressing your views online. i think it would be cool if unknown strangers found this mysterious webpage and agreed with some of the future posts&#xA;the goal is to go as MINIMAL AS POSSIBLE.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
